(Bernadette:)Yes.
No, no.
(Penny:)But in this case, yes.
(Amy:)Interesting.
(Amy:)And was it not satisfactory?
(Penny:)No, it was great.
(Penny:)He just didn't really challenge
me on an intellectual level.
(Bernadette:)Couldn't you just fool around
with him and then listen to NPR?
(Penny:)Wouldn't help. Zack
can't even spell NPR.
(Bernadette:)It's what I do with Howard.
(Bernadette:)I'm much smarter than he is.
(Bernadette:)But it's important
to protect his manhood.
(Amy:)Hoo.
(Bernadette:)What's the matter?
(Amy:)I'm suddenly feeling flushed.
(Amy:)My heart rate is elevated,
my palms are clammy,
(Amy:)my mouth is dry.
(Amy:)In addition, I keep
involuntarily saying "hoo."
(Penny:)Oh, we know what's
causing that, don't we?
(Amy:)It's no mystery.
(Amy:)I obviously have the flu
(Amy:)coupled with sudden-onset
Tourette's syndrome.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪